{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "That's Mr Bloyd,________ you wanted to meet.",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "which",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "That is the worst picture ________ I've ever seen.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The strike,________ lasted two months, is over at last.",
      "a": "whose",
      "b": "whom",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "who",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Who, whom, whose refer to person\n- Which refers to things",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The book ________ I bought yesterday is very interesting.",
      "a": "whom",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The President, ________ came by plane, held a press conference.",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "whom",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "what",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action)\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited\n- What:  used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain\n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The man ________ lives upstairs is very old.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "whose",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "who",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action)\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to)\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The man ________ you saw by the river is my dentist.",
      "a": "whom",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "to whom",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- We say \"see someone/something\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The meeting, ________ few people were invited, was a great success.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "whom",
      "c": "to which",
      "d": "what",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n-Whom: refer to person \n- Invite somebody to somewhere ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Those are the men and the carts ________ we saw on the way.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "whose",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you hear ________ she said last night?",
      "a": "that",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "what",
      "d": "whose",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Hear something ( what + clause)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}